Bro Snake, what are you doing?
You deserve the most credit for pulling this deal off.
But the cops are breathing down our necks lately.
Just lay low here for a while, alright?
You won't be short a single penny.
Wait, Bro Snake...
That's enough.
Bro Snake, I can still help!
Bro Snake!
The message has been sent,
but what about this dummy account?
Whatever it takes,
I have to find a way to get it to Sun Ming.
Bro.
It's you.
Thanks for speaking up for me last time.
You're a good guy.
Bro,
can you do me a favor?
Sure.
Really?
I have a USB drive here.
Can you find a way to get it out for me?
His name is Sun Ming.
He's a cop.
But he can help you get away from him.
Okay.
Really?
Here.
Freeze!
Right, right, right.
Bro.
It's safe here.
What's your name?
I'm Dandan.
Bro Dan.
Thanks for the help.
We're just grasping at straws here.
Let's hope it arrives safely.
Hello?
Director.
Our funds are already in place.
Are you ready to make the transfer?
Let me double-check.
Liu.
Have their funds arrived?
Director Cao's funds are indeed in place.
President Cao.
All right.
We can make the transfer now.
OK, Director Qin.
Once the money is in place,
I'll start construction according to your blueprints.
Great, great.
President Cao,
thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you.
Liu,
have finance make the transfer now.
Understood.
Captain Sun.
The Command Center received a report.
Someone found a banknote
with "Nursing Home 110" written on it.
A banknote?
Investigate all nursing homes in the city immediately.
See which one had major fund movements
or activities recently.
Yes, sir.
Hello? Is this the Social Welfare Center?
Sir.
Finance just transferred the money.
Please check it.
Bro Snake.
The police have started monitoring the nursing home's account.
Hello, Director Qin.
Have you
made the transfer?
President Cao,
we just transferred the funds.
Please check if you've received it.
Uncle.
My dear uncle.
Thanks for your four million!
Let's open a good bottle of wine.
On it.
Captain.
There's a Bright Nursing Home in the suburbs.
They're currently planning a second phase of construction.
What's their director's name?
Qin Changxian.
Here's the plan.
Contact the bank immediately
and have them monitor this nursing home's account.
Also, pull up
the surveillance footage from where it was reported.
Yes, sir.
Hello, the number you have dialed is not in service.
Not in service?
Let me dial again.
Hello, the number you have dialed is not in service.
It can't be out of service.
You try dialing it.
Let me do it.
Hello, the number you have dialed is not in service.
It's fine, I'll try again.
We've... been scammed.
We got scammed!
That can't be right.
We... we...
We went to his company and checked it out.
Something's definitely wrong.
Director Qin!
What's wrong?
Leave me alone.
Call the police.
OK, I'll do it right now.
The bank...
Xiao Lin, Zhou Hui.
Let's head to the nursing home immediately.
Yes, sir.
Hello, is this the police?
We've been scammed.
Yes.
We...
We've been scammed.
Hello, is this the bank?
Our account...
We've been scammed.
Our account number is 1233563.
Where is Director Qin?
He's inside.
Hurry!
He... he was just here.
This is bad. Follow me.
My dear brothers and sisters,
I've let you all down.
Director Qin!
Don't do anything rash! Come down!
Don't worry!
The nursing home's funds are safe!
Bro Snake.
Bro Snake!
Speak.
The money's gone.
What do you mean?
The four million is gone.
What happened?
There's a problem with his dummy account.
Any amount over one million is automatically returned in full.
Damn it!
Find Li Wen.
Director Qin.
Fortunately, we received the USB drive in time.
We saved the funds using the program loophole.
Really?
That's great!
Thank you.
Director Qin,
we've confirmed with the finance department.
Our money has basically been recovered.
Officers,
thank you so much.
Director Qin.
You really saved me.
You're welcome.
It's our job.
Thank you, thank you.
We also hope
the public can raise their awareness
and give scammers no opportunities.
Captain Sun.
By comparing the convenience store's security footage,
our colleagues have basically pinpointed their hideout.
Li Wen, you bastard!
Get out here!
Bro Snake,
why did you mess with the trading platform?
Who gave you the nerve?
Bro Snake,
my huge deal is completely gone.
Brother Liu, please say something for me!
Didn't we agree on this?
What are you doing?
Bro Liu,
what does he mean?
Bro Snake, he's talking nonsense.
You can't trust this guy.
Brother Liu,
you said as long as I tweaked the backend for you
and helped you skim some money,
you'd put in a good word for me with Bro Snake!
How could you lie to me?
Bro Liu.
Bro Snake,
to tell you the truth,
I swear I didn't do anything.
Don't you trust me?
Bro Snake,
I have proof.
Then I'll leave a backdoor in the program for you
so you can earn a bit more.
Are you serious?
It'll definitely work.
No one will ever know about this.
Also,
him making you lose face in front of everyone earlier
was just to pave the way for this deal, wasn't it?
Grass Snake is a piece of trash.
What does he know about the high-tech industry?
I'll take him down sooner or later.
I picked you up off the street
and fed you,
and this is how you repay me?
Bro Snake,
I just wanted to make some money back then.
I didn't expect things to turn out like this.
The police are here!
You two stall them!
Whoever survives gets major credit!
Hold them off!
Hold them off and you'll be Third-in-command!
Run, Bro Snake, Brother Liu!
Hurry and run!
I'll hold them off for you!
Freeze! Don't move!
Get down!
Take them away.
Those two bastards ran that way.
Go after them.
Xiao Lin!
Take a team and go.
Well, you look pretty relaxed sitting here.
I worried about you for nothing.
But,
good thing you got the dummy account's USB drive out in time.
That allowed us to ensure
the safety of the nursing home's account.
Thanks, Bro Dan.
That's because I'm smart.
That idiot Cao She
almost skinned me alive.
He tortured me every single day.
Look at these wounds.
Alright.
What are you doing?
It's for your own good.
Let's go.
Come back to the station with me.
I'm not going.
Not an option.
Fine, fine, fine.
Don't move!
Hands on your head!
How dare you come looking for me here?
My scheme got busted by the cops too.
What?
Didn't I tell you not to act rashly?
What did you do?
I targeted a nursing home.
Stupid!
Do you know whose nursing home that is?
The director is a model hero!
Did you think their money would be so easy to take?
Yes, Sir. I know I was wrong.
I had no other choice but to come to you!
I promise,
absolutely no one followed me.
I...
Go set up a new operation.
Thank you, Sir.
But you must promise me one thing.
Which is...